http://www.e-iceblue.com/privacypolicy.html

.NET.NET APIsSpire.Office for .NETSpire.OfficeViewer for .NETSpire.Doc for .NETSpire.DocViewer for .NETSpire.XLS for .NETSpire.Spreadsheet for .NETSpire.Presentation for .NETSpire.PDF for .NETSpire.PDFViewer for .NETSpire.PDFViewer for ASP.NETSpire.DataExport for .NETSpire.Barcode for .NETSpire.Email for .NETFree ProductsFree Spire.Office for .NETFree Spire.Doc for .NETFree Spire.DocViewer for .NETFree Spire.XLS for .NETFree Spire.Presentation for .NETFree Spire.PDF for .NETFree Spire.PDFViewer for .NETFree Spire.PDFConverter for .NETFree Spire.DataExport for .NETFree Spire.Barcode for .NETWPF APIsSpire.Office for WPFSpire.Doc for WPFSpire.DocViewer for WPFSpire.XLS for WPFSpire.PDF for WPFSpire.PDFViewer for WPFJAVAJAVA APIsSpire.Office for JavaSpire.Doc for JavaSpire.XLS for JavaSpire.Presentation for JavaSpire.PDF for JavaSpire.Barcode for JavaFree ProductsFree Spire.Office for JavaFree Spire.Doc for JavaFree Spire.XLS for JavaFree Spire.Presentation for JavaFree Spire.PDF for JavaFree Spire.Barcode for JavaAndroidAndroid APIsSpire.PDF for Android via JavaPurchaseOrder OnlineDownload CentrePurchase PoliciesRenewal PoliciesFind A ResellerPurchase FAQSSupport FAQsHow to Apply LicenseLicense AgreementPrivacy PolicySupportSample CenterTutorialsForumLive DemoCustomized DemoCode SamplesProgram GuideSpire.Doc for .NETSpire.Doc for JavaSpire.XLS for .NETSpire.XLS for JavaSpire.Presentation for .NETSpire.Presentation for JavaSpire.PDF for .NETSpire.PDF for JavaSpire.DataExportCorporationAbout UsContact UsPartnerBecome Our ResellerAffiliateOur ServiceOur CustomersReviews
Login/Register
Search
ZH-CN
This web site is maintained by E-iceblue Co., Ltd, also known as "E-iceblue", Room 601, Unit 5th in Kaile international, Chengdu, Sichuan, China. By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of the E-iceblue Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
When you visit this site, you may surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to analyze and improve our site, we use "Cookies" to track your visit to our site and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided E-iceblue with Personal Information. "Cookies" cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, therefore allowing you to decide whether or not to accept it.
Your Personal Information
E-iceblue takes online security seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy. In order to access some E-iceblue services you will be asked to provide personal identification information ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes any information that may be used to identify you, such as: first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, or other contact information that is provided to us by you, or any other party. In general, you may visit https://www.e-iceblue.com without disclosing to us who you are and without revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However without providing personal information you may not be able to download or purchase our products or services.
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to E-iceblue. However, when you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, E-iceblue may require that you provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is entirely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, E-iceblue may require that you provide certain personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.
Third Party Services
Your personal information will not be leased, sold, rented, or otherwise made available to any other third party except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws, police investigations, or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. Be aware that any personally identifiable information you elect to make publicly available on our Site or the E-iceblue Service, such as posting comments on our public forum, will be available to others and this privacy policy does not apply. If you remove information that you have made public on our Sites or Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or saved that information. Our forum is hosted on our own servers and we have full control over the data and ability to remove content if requested.
Security
Security
Wherever your Personal Information may be held by E-iceblue or by a third party on E-iceblue's behalf, reasonable and appropriate precautions, such as encryption, firewalls and like technologies, are and will be implemented to protect such Personal Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access.
Sensitive Information
We do not collect Sensitive Information such as medical, health, racial, ethnic, political, religious, philosophic, union membership, or sexual orientation information. If we are made aware that we have received such information, we will promptly proceed to its deletion.
Children's Privacy
E-iceblue are not designed nor structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child under the age of thirteen, we will promptly delete this information.
Aggregate Information
The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain Personal Information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this aggregate information with third parties to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences.
Your Consent
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to E-iceblue's processing of Personal Information for the purposes outlined above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our website for a reasonable period of time.
twitter_1
skype_1
youtube_1
facebook_1
forum_1
Purchase
Order Online
Purchase FAQs
e-iceblue. All Rights Reserved.
